<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Mobility Profile</string>
    <string name="allow_access">Allow Mobility Profile access to:</string>
    <string name="checkbox_GPS">GPS</string>
    <string name="checkbox_calendar">Read calendar</string>
    <string name="checkbox_tracking">Start continuous location tracking</string>
    <string name="info">is an app which magically offers your next destination to your favourite journey planner ;)</string>
    <string name="permissions_info">
        Mobility Profile needs permissions to read your calendar and access your location.\n\n
        Calendar is used to get your next probable destination from your events.\n\n
        With location data Mobility Profile will learn to predict destinations.
    </string>
    <string name="last_places">Your last searched places</string>
    <string name="favourites_title">Your favourite places</string>
    <string name="favourites_name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="favourites_address_hint">Address</string>
    <string name="favourites_button">Add</string>
    <string name="favourites_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="favourites_delete_title">Delete this favourite place?</string>
    <string name="favourites_edit_title">Edit this favourite place</string>
    <string name="edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="reset_button_text">Reset app and delete all data</string>
    <string name="reset_title">Delete all collected data?</string>
    <string name="reset_message">Deletes all collected data, including visited locations, searched routes, and favourite places.</string>
    <string name="reset_ok">Delete</string>
    <string name="reset_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="custom_permission_info">Allows the software to use information provided by Mobility Profile. Exact data collected by Mobility Profile won\'t be shared, only suggestions Mobility Profile is giving based on that data.</string>
    <string name="conflict_header">The following applications have defined conflicting permissions with Mobility Profile:\n</string>
    <string name="conflict_info">If two or more applications define the same permission, the application that is installed first is the one whose definition is used. Applications listed above were installed before Mobility Profile and have defined the same permission as Mobility Profile. To solve the problem, uninstall those applications, then run Mobility Profile and make sure this message is no longer shown. After that you can reinstall those applications.
        \n\nMore information about the problem can be found at https://datatheorem.github.io/2014/04/16/custom-permissions/</string>
</resources>
